Congrats on finishing the course!
Hopefully you have picked up
some skills on how to build,
evaluate, and iterate on
your RAG application to make it
more production-ready. Regardless
of whether you come from a
data science machine
learning background or
a traditional software
background, you'll need
to learn some of these core development principles
so that you can
be a rock-star AI engineer
who can build robust LLM
software systems.
Reducing LLM hallucination is
going to be the
top priority for every
developer as the field evolves.
We are excited to
see the base models
get better and larger-scale
evaluations become cheaper
and more accessible
for everyone to set up and
run.
As a next step, I'd
recommend looking more
deeply into understanding
your data pipeline, retrieval
strategy, and
LLM prompts to help
improve RAG performance. These
two techniques we showed
were just the tip
of the iceberg. You
should look into everything
from chunk sizes to
retrieval techniques like hybrid
search to LLM-based reasoning
like chain of thought.
The RAG triad is
an excellent place to
start with evaluating your RAG-based
LLM apps. As a next step, I
encourage you to dig
deeper into the area
of evaluating LLMs and
the apps that they power. This
includes topics such as
assessing model confidence, calibration,
uncertainty, explainability,
privacy, fairness, and
toxicity in both benign
and adversarial settings.
We look forward to
seeing what you build next.